[
    {
        "question": "Which is the correct syntax of JavaScript typeof operator?",
        "options": [
            "typeof variable/value",
            "typeof(variable/value)",
            "Both A. and B.",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Both A. and B."
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following JavaScript code?\n\n```js\nvar x = 12.34;\ndocument.getElementById(\"test\").innerHTML = typeof(x);\n```",
        "options": [
            "int",
            "float",
            "long",
            "number"
        ],
        "answer": "number"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to define a JavaScript function?",
        "options": [
            "module",
            "fun",
            "func",
            "function"
        ],
        "answer": "function"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the correct syntax for the function definition?",
        "options": [
            "return_type function function_name(parameter1, parameter2, ...) { /*Function's body*/ }",
            "function function_name(parameter1, parameter2, ...) { /*Function's body*/ }",
            "return_type function_name(parameter1, parameter2, ...) { /*Function's body*/ }",
            "function function_name(parameter1, parameter2, ...) as return_type { /*Function's body*/ }"
        ],
        "answer": "function function_name(parameter1, parameter2, ...) { /*Function's body*/ }"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following JavaScript code?\n\n```js\nfunction addition(a, b) {\n    return a+b;\n}\ndocument.getElementById(\"test\").innerHTML = addition;\n```",
        "options": [
            "SyntaxError",
            "ValueError",
            "0",
            "function addition(a, b) { return a+b; }"
        ],
        "answer": "function addition(a, b) { return a+b; }"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can we use a function as a variable value?",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In JavaScript a variable contains one value while an object may contain ___.",
        "options": [
            "One value",
            "Two values",
            "Three values",
            "Many values"
        ],
        "answer": "Many values"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the correct syntax to access an object property in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
            "objectName:propertyName",
            "propertyName",
            "objectName[\"propertyName\"]",
            "Both B. and C."
        ],
        "answer": "Both B. and C."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which property is used to get the length of a string in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
            "strlen",
            "len",
            "length",
            "Length"
        ],
        "answer": "length"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following JavaScript code?\n\n```js\nlet str = \"IncludeHelp\";\ndocument.getElementById(\"test\").innerHTML = str.length;\n```",
        "options": [
            "11",
            "12",
            "ValueError",
            "SyntaxError"
        ],
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is used to break up a code line within a text string in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
            "Single quote (')",
            "Single backslash (\\')",
            "Backslashes (\\\\)",
            "Back-ticks (``)"
        ],
        "answer": "Single backslash (\\')"
    },
    {
        "question": "Will the following JavaScript code work?\n\n```js\ndocument.getElementById(\"test\").innerHTML = \\\n    \"Hello, IncludeHelp!\";\n```",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the correct JavaScript statement to define string as object?",
        "options": [
            "var s = new String(\"IncludeHelp!\");",
            "var s = String(\"IncludeHelp!\");",
            "var s = \"IncludeHelp!\"",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "var s = new String(\"IncludeHelp!\");"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following JavaScript code?\n\n```js\nlet str1 = new String(\"IncludeHelp!\");\nlet str2 = new String(\"IncludeHelp!\");\ndocument.getElementById(\"test\").innerHTML = (str1==str2);\n```",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is/are the valid JavaScript method(s) to extract string parts?",
        "options": [
            "slice(start, end)",
            "substring(start, end)",
            "substr(start, length)",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following JavaScript code?\n\n```js\nlet x = \"Hello, IncludeHelp!\";\ndocument.getElementById(\"test\").innerHTML = x.slice(-13,-1);\n```",
        "options": [
            "IncludeHelp!",
            "IncludeHelp",
            "ValueError",
            "Hello,"
        ],
        "answer": "IncludeHelp"
    },
    {
        "question": "In JavaScript, the string template literals use ____ rather than the quotes (\"\") to define a string?",
        "options": [
            "Single quotes ('')",
            "Single backslash (\\'\\')",
            "Backslashes (\\\\)",
            "Back-ticks (``)"
        ],
        "answer": "Back-ticks (``)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does the following JavaScript variable definition is correct?\n\n```js\nlet x = `I'm \"David!\"`;\n```",
        "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which JavaScript method is used to get a number as a string?",
        "options": [
            "toString()",
            "intToString()",
            "parseInteger()",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "toString()"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following JavaScript code?\n\n```js\nconst myArray = ['h', 'e', 'l', 'l', 'o'];\ndocument.write(myArray[0]);\ndocument.write(myArray[1]);\n```",
        "options": [
            "he",
            "undefinedh",
            "ValueError",
            "TypeError"
        ],
        "answer": "he"
    }
]
